BRYSON COONS

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT

757-274-7687

coonsbrysona@gmail.com www.brysoncoons.com

SKILLS

- Proficiency in HTML CSS& Javascript, C++, C#,Python, and SQL
- Trained user of VCS's such as GitHub
- Communication and problem resolution with peers

EDUCATION

Tidewater Community
College

2020-2023

- -AS in Computer Science -3.8 GPA
- Avid member / contributor to the Software Development Club

Old Dominion University

2024-Current

-Pursuing BS in Computer Science

PROFILE

Full-stack software engineer with a wide range of professional experience from web application development, independent video game development, small-scale network management, information technology, and Computer-Aided Design. I have a particular interest in accessibility of technology to people with disabilities and Artificial Intelligence technology.

EXPERIENCE

Full-Stack Web Developer

2021-2024

Developed and maintained web applications for individual clients, small businesses, and organizations for many purposes. Exercised knowledge of front-end languages and UI/UX experience as well as applications of back-end technologies such as user account systems, database management, and version control through GitHub.

AutoCAD Survey Technician at AlphaTec Surveyors

2020-2024

Managed the creation, revision, and delivery of Automated Machine Guidance models to Land Development Companies. Used problem solving and critical thinking to engineer solutions to complex 3D issues, such as drainage systems and building construction. Demonstrated clear and concise communication and management skills when coordinating work between field crews and other employees in the CAD department.

CERTIFICATIONS

CompTIA A+, Network+, and Security+